# **DENITSA PESHEVA**

s-Hertogenbosch, the Netherlands • dpessheva@gmail.com

in linkedin.com/in/denitsa-pesheva-94037a105/ 🖸 github.com/Dpessheva



# Junior software developer

### Professional background

I have a little more than a year and a half programming experience. One year in a Web developer program at Software University in Bulgaria, and seven months as a junior software developer. I have built a good basis of knowledge to start with, but I want to continue growing by gaining real-life experience in software development.

# **Key Competencies & Offerings**

- Javascript
- Typescript
- HTML5
- CSS3
- SASS

- NodeJS
- Express
- Angular
- Firebase
- Google Cloud Platform

- Jira
- Scrum
- Visual Studio code

Soft Skills

- Emotional intelligence
- Quick learner
- Self-starter
- Team player
- Good communication skills

#### Selected work experience

Jul 2019 - Jan 2020

Junior Software Developer

Zaapps, Eindhoven, the Netherlands

As a part of the development team of Zzapps, I have participated in different projects. It helped me to gain real-life experience in software development with tools like Angular, TypeScript, Firebase, NodeJs, Google could platform and a few more.

- Refactoring, bugs-fixing
- Back-end development with Nodejs and Firebase
- Front-end

Feb 2017 - Dec 2017

Data analyst internship

Effective Profiles, Gouda, the Netherlands

- Engaged in a project for identifying duplicated profiles in the database
- Engaged in a project for customers segmentation
- Reports and data visualization

• Polls • Reports Headhunting Marketing internship March 2014 - June 2014 Getlokal, Sofia, Bulgaria • Writing website content • Brand development • Reaching new clients Education JavaScript Web Developer 2018 - 2019 Software University 2015 - 2017 Communication and Information Technology (MSc) Tilburg University Human Aspects of Information Technology 2011 - 2015 Psychology (BSc) New Bulgarian University Organizational Psychology Languages Bulgarian Native English Professional working proficiency Dutch Elementary proficiency Created with 📅 VisualCV

Feb 2015 - March 2015

Human Resources internship

As an intern, I was focused on:

Address Real Estate, Sofia Bulgaria